[{"answer": "Good.  Let's fool around.  Now, I'll be the innocent little milk maid and you'll be the naughty stable boy.  Oh, this milk is so heavy.  I'll never reach the house.  Help.  Will someone help me", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " We can't play today", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Wait.  Wait.  We can't play today. I have too many appointments", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Thursday.  Thursday.  We'll play Thursday.  We'll play the Contessa and the chauffeur", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "According to the backer's list you raised", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It makes a great deal of difference. That's fraud.  If they found out, you could go to prison", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "See?  You could have raised a million dollars, put on a sixty thousand dollar flop and kept the rest", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, you'd go to jail.  If the play were a hit, you'd have to pay off the backers, and with so many backers there could never be enough profits to go around, get it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Aha, aha, aha, aha, aha, aha!!  So, in order for the scheme to work, we'd have to find a sure fire flop", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What scheme?  Your scheme, you bloody little genius", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Let me see ... it's such a beautiful day.  Why waste it indoors.  I've got it!  Let's go to that place! We'll lunch at the sea shore", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What's the matter, my friend?  Don't you like that place", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's the matter, my friend?  Don't you like that place", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Nonsense!  As far as that place and Marks are concerned, you're working with my friend, right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " \"I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy ..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "My play?  You mean,", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I solemnly swear..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "By the sacred memory..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "By the sacred memory..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Of Siegfried..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Of Siegfried..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Nietzche..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Bismark..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hindenburg..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The Graf Spee..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "The Graf Spee..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The Blue Max..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The Blue Max..", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And last, but not least, my friend... you know who", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "And last, but not least, my friend... you know who", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Heil you know who", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "And last, but not least, my friend... you know who", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Heil you know who", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Stop talking like that, you white mouse!  Nothing's going to go wrong. As a matter of fact, today I have taken steps to insure total disaster. At two o'clock we have an appointment with none other than my friend", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend is the worst director that ever lived", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Call chauffeur.  Get car", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No.  We go.", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Good.  Good.  We go Motel", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You, my friend go Motel", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You, my friend go Motel", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Get car.  Get car", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Just think, yesterday I was a meaningless little accountant", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "To failure", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Baby, why does he keep saying baby? I didn't write baby.  The Fuhrer never said baby.  Vat is it vit this baby", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You shut up!  I'm the author. You're just the audience.  I outrank you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " \"By the light, by the light", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "\"Of the silvery mooooon", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "\"Of the silvery mooooon", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "\"He wants to croon, he wants to croon", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "We have, your honor", "docId": "producers.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "We find the defendants incredibly guilty", "qsentId": 52}]